{
    "subject": "resource/Steam_Powered_Giraffe",
    "predicate": "ontology/hometown",
    "object": "resource/United_States",
    "human_readable": "The hometown of Steam Powered Giraffe is United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8987013697624207,
            "question": "What country is considered the hometown of Steam Powered Giraffe?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.815853476524353,
            "question": "Where is Steam Powered Giraffe from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6731253266334534,
            "question": "Where are Steam Powered Giraffe originally based?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6704031229019165,
            "question": "What is the nationality of Steam Powered Giraffe?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5531467199325562,
            "question": "In what nation did Steam Powered Giraffe originate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5510264039039612,
            "question": "Can you tell me the origin country of Steam Powered Giraffe?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5152742862701416,
            "question": "What is the home country of the band Steam Powered Giraffe?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46708065271377563,
            "question": "Which country is associated with Steam Powered Giraffe's roots?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4222466051578522,
            "question": "If you were to say where Steam Powered Giraffe is from, what would you say?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41000276803970337,
            "question": "Steam Powered Giraffe hails from which part of the world?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The hometown of Steam Powered Giraffe is United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8807_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=If you were to say where Steam Powered Giraffe is from, what would you say?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8807_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which country is associated with Steam Powered Giraffe's roots?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8807_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the home country of the band Steam Powered Giraffe?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8807_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8807_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8807_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8807_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8807_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8807_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8807_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8807_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8807_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8807_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8807_87.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents mention that Steam Powered Giraffe is based in San Diego, California, which is in the United States. Therefore, the statement that their hometown is the United States is supported by the provided context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}